skipthedishes.com 2018-12-25

# SkipTheDishes

("SkipTheDishes" or "Skip", "we", "us", "our", etc) 

## Skip Platform Privacy Policy

_SkipTheDishes Restaurant Services Inc. and SkipTheDishes, Corp._ take privacy and data security seriously. We are committed to transparency in the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes how we use personal information, and the circumstances under which we may share this information with a third party. This Privacy Policy applies to the privacy practices of Skip on our website located at: www.skipthedishes.com, or the various associated websites, platforms or applications (collectively and each individually, the **"Skip Platform"** ) but does not include personal information relating to employees in such a capacity.  As an organization engaged in commercial activities, we are committed to complying with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act Canada, and with any other Canadian privacy laws applicable to our operations.  By visiting and/or using the Skip Platform, you consent to the collection, use, storage, disclosure and transfer of your personal information as set out in this policy. In some cases, we may ask you to provide explicit consent if we intend to collect, use or disclose your personal information otherwise than as indicated in this Privacy Policy, however sometimes your consent may be implied through your conduct with us.  If you do not agree with any part of this Privacy Policy you should not conduct any transactions on the Skip Platform, navigate away from the Skip Platform immediately, and uninstall our application. 

### _Collection and Use of Personal Information_

### ● Account Creation:

We collect your name, phone number, email address, a password of your selection, the date and time of account creation and the IP address of the device used for account creation. We use this information to administer your account, to enable your access to the Skip Platform, verify your identity as an authorized user concerning any accounts, and to implement, carry out and maintain security measures aimed at protecting our customers from identity theft, fraud and unauthorized access to an account. You may choose to register for an account via a third- party social media network, including Facebook and Google+ ("Social Media"). If you do so, you authorize us to access certain Social Media account information consistent with your Social Media privacy settings, including your name. We use this information to administer your account, and to enable your access to the Skip Platform. 

### ● Social Media:

We may offer you the opportunity to otherwise engage with Skip or its content on or through Social Media. When you engage with us through Social Media websites, plug-ins and applications, you may allow us to have access to and disclose certain information associated with your Social Media account (e.g., name, username, email address, profile picture) to deliver content or as part of the operation of the website, plug-in or application. 

### ● Placing an Order:

We collect information relating to any orders you place on the Skip Platform, including the IP address of the device used to place the order to help protect against theft, fraud and unauthorized access to an account, and payment information (e.g. your credit card number) using the secure services of our payment processors. Payment operations are outsourced to our payment processors and we do not store your credit card information in our systems other than the first four and last four digits of the credit card number.  If your order has been placed for delivery, we collect the physical address to which you have requested delivery. We use this information to complete your delivery, and to allow you to select previously entered addresses for future deliveries. If you submit an order for alcohol, we may verify your government-issued identification to confirm that you are of legal age. 

### ● Gift Cards:

When you purchase a gift card for use on the Skip Platform, we collect your payment card information (including payment card number, security code, expiration date, cardholder name and billing address) using the secure services of our payment processors for the purposes of processing your payment. We also collect the gift card recipient’s email address and any information contained in the message to the recipient. We use this information to deliver and manage the gift card. 

### ● Order History:

We may collect your order history including the date, time, cost, order type (takeout or delivery order), physical address and delivery instructions (if a delivery order), method of purchase, and order details, including specific food items ordered and special order instructions. We use this information to ensure that your order has been completed and to improve our service offerings. 

### ● Marketing Communications:

We may use your personal information to contact you for your views regarding Skip and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to the Skip Platform, products, services or your account. You cannot opt out of receiving notifications of important changes or developments (e.g. to this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Service/Use) unless you discontinue use of the Skip Platform.  You agree that we may use your personal information to let you know about our other events, products and services that may be of interest to you including services that may be the subject of direct marketing. We may contact you to do so by telephone, SMS/MMS and email and if you use our mobile application, via push notification. It is always your choice whether to receive or to continue receiving such marketing materials and updates from Skip. We will not send you any direct marketing communications unless you have separately consented to receive such communications or such consent has been deemed to have been given under applicable law. If you no longer wish to receive direct marketing communications, you can opt-out using the unsubscribe mechanism in the marketing communication itself (e.g. by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of an email or by replying with the word “STOP” to an SMS/MMS or by following other provided instructions). To manage push notifications, go to the settings page of your phone or tablet and change the push notification permission for the Skip app. If you switch off in-app push notifications, you will no longer receive updates on your orders via push. 

### ● Reviews:

We may offer you the opportunity to submit a review on the Skip Platform. When your review is published, the content and the given name you entered when creating your account will be publicly displayed. You also consent to us using such reviews in any marketing or advertising materials. 

### ● Referrals:

The referral, "refer a friend" and other similar features on the Skip Platform permit you to send an email to other individuals that may be interested in Skip. This feature may require you to submit your name and email address, as well as the name and email address of the recipient. We do not use the names or email addresses submitted in these circumstances for any other purpose without the consent of you or the email recipient to do so. Please ensure that you only submit email addresses of individuals with whom you have a personal or family relationship and who would want to receive the message. 

### ● Employment Opportunities:

In connection with a job application or related inquiry, you may provide us with personal information including a resume, cover letter, or similar employment-related materials. This information will be used for the purposes of processing and responding to your application for current and future career opportunities, and to manage any ongoing working relationship. 

### ● Become a Courier:

You may apply to become an independently contracted courier by providing us with your name, phone number, email address, physical address, driver’s license, vehicle insurance and registration, proof of work eligibility, banking information as well as other contractor-related materials. We use this information for the purpose of processing and responding to your application, and to manage any ongoing contractor relationship. 

### ● Apply to Become a Restaurant or Vendor:

You may apply to become a vendor on the Skip Platform by providing us with your name, phone number, email address, physical address as well as other vendor materials. In most instances, this information is not considered personal information. We use this information for the purpose of processing and responding to your application, and to manage any ongoing vendor relationship. 

### ● Surveys and Customer Research:

From time to time, Skip may offer you the opportunity to participate in one of our surveys or other customer research, or to provide feedback regarding your order. The information obtained through our surveys and customer research is used in an aggregated, non-personally identifiable form to help us understand our customers and to enhance our product and service offerings. 

### ● Contests and Promotions:

When you enter a contest or participate in a promotion, Skip may collect your name, address, phone number, email address, and other information you provide. This information is used to administer your participation in the contest, sweepstakes or promotion. 

### ● Contact Us:

When you contact us with a comment or question, we collect the information you provide such as your name and email address, along with additional information that we may need to help us promptly respond to your inquiry. We retain this information to assist you in the future and to improve our customer service and service offerings. We also use personal information to establish and manage our relationship with you and provide quality service. We may record voice calls for training and quality purposes. 

### _Information We Collect Automatically_

We and our third-party service providers, including Google Analytics, collect, process, store and analyze information obtained from your browser when you visit the Skip Platform, including IP address, your location when the Skip mobile application is used, device identifiers, browser characteristics, operating system details, language preferences, referring URLs, length of visits and pages viewed. We also use "cookies" or other tools that track, measure and analyze the behaviors and usage patterns of visitors to the Skip Platform. We use this information to help us understand how visitors engage with the Skip Platform and to improve our visitors’ experience.  A cookie is a tiny element of data that the Skip Platform can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your web browser or mobile device so we can recognize you when you return. The information that cookies collect includes the date and time of your visit, your registration information, session identification number, and your navigational history and preferences.  We use cookies for analytics purposes as well as for certain features of the Skip Platform. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many major browsers and smartphones are initially set up to accept them. You may set your web browser or smartphone to notify you when you receive a cookie or to not accept certain cookies. However, if you decide not to accept cookies from the Skip Platform, you may not be able to take advantage of all its features.  Some third-party service providers may use cookies on our site. We have no control over those cookies and they are not covered by this Privacy Policy.  You can obtain additional information on Google Analytics’ collection and processing of data and data privacy and security, including how to learn more about opting out of Google Analytics’ data collection. 

### _Interest-Based Advertising_

We use cookies and other technologies for interest-based advertising purposes.  To learn more about Interest-Based Advertising, or to opt out of online interest-based advertising from a list of companies participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada at any time, visit <http://youradchoices.ca/choices>.  To learn more about Interest-Based Advertising in mobile apps and to opt out of this type of advertising by third-party advertising companies that participate in the DAAC’s AppChoices tool, please download the version of AppChoices for your device at <https://youradchoices.ca/appchoices/>.  On your mobile device, you may also have a “Limit Ad Tracking” setting (in iOS devices) or a setting to “Opt-out of Interest-Based Ads” (on Android), which allows you to limit the use of information about your use of apps for purposes of serving ads targeted to your interests.  Please be aware that, even if you opt out of interest-based advertising, you may continue to receive ads from us, but they will not be served using interest-based information about you. Also, to successfully opt out, you must have cookies enabled in your web browser. If your browser is configured to reject cookies when you visit these opt-out webpages, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different device or web browser, your opt-out instruction may not, or may no longer, be effective.  Your opt-out selections only apply to the web browser you use so you must opt out of each web browser on each device that you use. Once you opt out, if you delete your browser’s saved cookies, you may need to opt out again. 

### _Custom Audience_

We may also use services provided by third-party platforms (such as Social Media and other websites) to serve targeted advertisements on such platforms to you or others, and we may provide a hashed version of your email address or other information to the platform provider for such purposes. To opt out of the use of your information for such purposes, please contact us at privacy@skipthedishes.com.  We may use Social Media, or other third parties, to serve Custom Audience Ads on their platforms. You may be able to set your preferences for advertisements through your account settings on the platforms. 

### _Disclosure of Personal Information_

The personal information you provide to us will be held on our servers which may be in or outside Canada. In addition, your personal information may be accessed by or given to our staff working outside Canada and/or to third parties including companies within the JUST EAT group of companies (which means our subsidiaries and affiliates, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries and affiliates) who act for us for the purposes set out in this policy or for other purposes notified to you. For example, we may send personal information outside of Canada for processing and storage by other companies within the JUST EAT group of companies or by their service providers.  While your personal information is out of Canada, it is subject to the laws of the country in which it is held, and may be subject to disclosure to the governments, courts or law enforcement or regulatory agencies of such other country, pursuant to the laws of such country. Certain countries outside Canada and the European Economic Area do not always have equivalent strong data protection laws irrespective of the safeguards we have put in place for the protection of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  The third parties with whom we share your information may undertake various activities such as processing credit card payments and providing services or products for us. In addition, we may need to provide your personal information to any vendors that a customer has placed an order with and couriers to allow the your order to be process and delivered. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your personal information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  If you have consented we may allow select third parties, including marketing and advertising companies, our affiliates and associates, to contact you occasionally about other products or services that may be of interest to you. They may contact you by mail, telephone, mobile messaging (e.g. SMS, MMS, etc.) as well as by e-mail. If you change your mind about being contacted by these parties in the future, please let us know by using the contact details set out at the end of this Privacy Policy and/or by amending your profile accordingly.  If our business enters into a joint venture with, purchases or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your personal information may be disclosed or transferred to the target company, our new business partners or owners or their advisors provided that the information disclosed continues to be used for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy by the entity acquiring the information.  We may use the personal information that you provide to us if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with (and/or where we believe we are under a duty to comply with) any applicable legal obligation; or in order to enforce the Terms of Service/Use and any other agreement we have with you. This includes exchanging personal information with other companies and other organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and prevention.We and our service providers may use or disclose your personal information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to another organization for the purposes of investigating a breach of an agreement or contravention of law or detecting, suppressing or preventing fraud, or as otherwise required or permitted by applicable law or legal process. Your personal information may also be used or disclosed where necessary or desirable for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims and to investigate or prevent actual or suspected loss or harm to persons or property. 

### _Safeguarding and Retention of Personal Information_

We have implemented administrative, technical and physical measures to protect your personal information from unauthorised access and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We restrict access to your personal information to Skip personnel and authorized service providers who require access to fulfill their job requirements.  We will keep your information where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, while you hold an account with us or to enable us to meet our legal, tax or accounting obligations). We may retain certain data as necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personal information, or account recovery, or if required or permitted by law. All retained personal information will remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you request that your name be removed from our databases, it may not be possible to completely delete all your personal information due to technological and legal constraints.  The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will take steps to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information or other data transmitted to the Skip Platform; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your personal information, we will use organizational and technical safeguards to try to prevent unauthorised access. Please also note that the Skip Platform contains links to third party websites, which are not governed by this Privacy Policy, and JUST EAT is not responsible for the collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information by such third party websites. When you click on such a link, you will leave our service and go to another site. During this process, another entity may collect personal information from you. 

### _Access to Personal Information and Withdrawal of Consent_

You have the right to access, update and correct inaccuracies in your personal information in our custody and control, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law. You may request access, updating and corrections of inaccuracies in other personal information we have in our custody or control by emailing or writing to us at the contact information set out below. We may request certain personal information for the purposes of verifying the identity of the individual seeking access to their personal information records and may restrict access to personal information as required or permitted by applicable law or legal process.  You may withdraw or modify your consent at any time, subject to legal and contractual restrictions, provided that reasonable notice is given to us. If you withdraw your consent to receive information regarding certain products, publications, services or events being offered by Skip, you will no longer receive such communications. 

### _Updates to the Privacy Policy_

This Privacy Policy is current as of the “Last Updated” date which appears at the top of the page. Your continued use of the Skip Platform after any change of our Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the revised terms of this Privacy Policy.  We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time as required to reflect changes to our privacy practices. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

### _Contact Us_

Skip welcomes your comments, concerns and questions regarding this Privacy Policy and the use of your personal information. If you would like access to your information, if you have any comments, queries or requests relating to our use of your personal information or if you find any errors in our information about you, please contact us at:  SkipTheDishes Restaurant Services Inc.  
800 - 136 Market Avenue  
Winnipeg, Manitoba  
R3B 0P4  or by email at [privacy@skipthedishes.com](mailto:privacy@skipthedishes.com)  
Last Updated: August 08, 2018
